驾驶本和登记... 证
License and regis... tration.
给你 林警
Here you go, Rangers.
不好意思 女士
Excuse us, Ma'am.
- 诶我去 你看她多难... - 漂亮是吧? 是啊
- Oh, shit. Did you see how ug... - Beautiful she is? Yeah.
漂亮? Steve 她长得和你一个德行 就是咪咪小了点
Beautiful? Steve, she looks just like you, but with smaller titties.
裤裆管好了 Denzel 我先看到她的
Keep it in your pants, Denzel. I saw her first.
我撞到什么了么?
Oh, did I hit something?
只有我的心 用你的爱情之箭
Only my heart with your arrow of love.
还有这些动物
And also all these animals.
救命
Help me.
不好意思 我刚看书来着 我一开车就觉得很无聊
Sorry, I was just reading a book. I get so bored when I drive.
维戈·莫特森千层面烹制1001法
(丹麦裔美籍男电影演员)
维戈·莫特森和千层面? 我最爱的两样
Viggo Mortensen and lasagna? My two favorite things!
我是Steve Williams
Hi. I'm Steve Williams.
月度最佳林警 我肯定你听说过我
Ranger of the month. I'm sure you've heard of me.
我是月度最佳林警 Steve Williams
I'm ranger of the month. Steve Williams.
我叫Stephanie Bridges 在Hazelhurst小学任教
I'm Stephanie Bridges. I teach at Hazelhurst Elementary.
我很愿意一位威武有刚的林警有空去我的课堂上做报告
I would love to have a big, powerful ranger come and speak to my class sometime.
威武林警? 我也想见识一下
A Power Ranger? I want to see that.
威武林警要去我的课堂做报告?
A Power Ranger is speaking to my class?
真想不到 太好了
I didn't know about that. Awesome.
这俩贱人要是敢有孩子 我特么一砖头拍死那个孽畜
If these mother[Bleep] have a baby, I'm hitting that bitch with a brick.
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
谢谢你过来帮我网上约会 Connie
Thanks for helping me with computer dating, Connie.
翻译 白云苍狗
- 真是我好闺蜜 - 我愿为你做任何事的 Ethel
- You're such a good friend. - I'd do anything for you, Ethel.
翻译 偏执绝非过错
- 我知道 - 任何事
- I know. - Anything.
是啦 我懂的
Uh, yeah. Got it.
- 任何事 - 懂了
- Anything. - Got it!
不 不 真心的
No. No, seriously.
- 任何... - 我知道 靠 但愿这次能成
- Anyth... - I know! God, I hope this works.
翻译 井脑湿
为毛我的桃花运非得这么烂?
Why do I have such bad luck with men?
也许是你一直就没找对人
Maybe you've just been dating the wrong people.
啥? 别傻了
What? Don't be silly.
所以我崇拜撒旦
And that's why I worship Satan.
开玩笑的
Kidding.
好想用你这块人皮做张吊床出来
I'd love to make a hammock out of your skin.
♪ 我喜欢蕊蕊 ♪
♪ I like vagina. ♪
这个犹太人能吃不?
Is this kosher?
让你说着了
Ugh, you're right.
翻译 Chubby
我姐嫁了个超好的人家
My sister has the perfect marriage,
后期 旗木&盖罗
我却只能窝这儿在网上玩一夜情
and I'm on the Internet playing date rape roulette.
分类广告网站
你说Craigslist啊?
Oh, you mean Craigslist.
嘿 等下 这家伙看起来不错
Hey, wait. This guy seems perfect.
强壮 有激情 想要组建家庭
Strong, passionate, wants a family.
愿为对方做任何事
Willing to do anything.
任何事 任何事
Anything. Anything.
等一下 这人是你
Wait a minute. It's you.
我怎么跑那儿去了?
How'd that get on there?
要不要这么搞笑?
Isn't that hilarious?
我还以为找着合适的人了 弄半天原来是你
I mean, I thought it was someone perfect for me, and it was just you.
是啊 真搞笑
Yeah. That's hilarious.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
Connie 快来帮我
Connie, I really need you.
太好了 太好了
Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
快看这人 超帅 还有车呢
Look at this guy. He's handsome, he owns a car.
看呐 只有两个室友... 他爸和他妈
Oh, and look. Only two roommates... his mother and father.
他还想邀请我去豪华餐厅呢
And he wants to take me to a fancy restaurant.
食物救济站 服务社区 始自1975
话说吧 这倒让我想起
You know, that reminds me.
我到了该打算要小孩的年龄了
I'm hitting the age where I'd like to have kids.
是啊 我也很想打小孩
Yeah, I like hitting kids too.
谁特么欠揍 快给老子上点玉米面包
Who do I gotta [Bleep] up the ass to get some corn bread?
我一边上那婊子 她就一边生了
So the broad gives birth as I'm banging her.
应该算得上3P了 对吧?
That counts as a threesome, right?
- 又拖你孩子的赡养费了 Ken - 什么?
- You're late on your child support payments, Ken. - What?
我都不认识你好吧
I don't even know you.
告那小秃子 爸爸祝他生日快乐
Tell Alopecia daddy said Happy Birthday.
你知道吗? 我得走了
You know what? I'm out of here!
宝贝 宝贝儿 不好意思 我只不过是想让你印象深刻
Baby, baby. I'm sorry. I just made that up to impress you.
我们能重新开始吗? 我会把你料理得妥妥的
Can we start over? I'll treat you the way you deserve.
hard含有难/硬双意
快 我现在比中国数学题还要硬
Hurry up. I'm harder than Chinese math.
- 过来坐莲 - 你说啥 Ken?
- Sit on my penis. - What's that, Ken?
闭嘴 妈 正在性头上呢
Shut up, ma! I'm about to get some!
宝贝儿 我要和你做一整晚...
Oh, baby. I'm gonna make love to you all ni...
好吧 过劲了
Okay, I'm done.
- 最次把我送回家好么? - 天 好吧
- Can I at least get a ride home? - Jeez, fine.
妈
Mom!
送她回家
Give her a ride home!
我是一位...
I am a...
公... 园...
Pa... pa... park...
你俩白痴干特么啥呢?
What the hell are you two idiots up to?
公园发生了三起蛇伤人事件 一头麋鹿被露营者给上了
We've had three snake attacks, a camper vandalized a moose,
我还在个火坑里发现了颗人头
and I found a human head in the fire pit!
你说是"人头"? 好希望是Connie的
Did you say "human"? Aw, I was hoping it was Connie's.
总有天我会了结你 Malloy
I'm gonna kill you one day, Malloy.
- 啥玩意儿? - 没啥
- What? - Uh, nothing.
各位 能小点声吗? 人家在为Stephanie的校园报告做准备呢
Guys, could you keep it down? I'm trying to practice my speech for Stephanie's school.
早上好 孩子们
Good morning, boys and girls.
- 我叫... - 超级大白痴?
- My name is... - Hanukkah Jizz Tonsil?
对的 我叫超级大白痴
Yes. My name is Hanukkah Jizz Tonsil.
等等 才不是呢
Wait. No it's not.
等下 难道是? 你妹
Wait. Is it? Shoot.
他真心样样事都好操蛋
He's awful at literally everything.
我是公园林...
I am a park ra...
- 相信孩子们会喜欢的 - 抱歉 迟到了
- I think the kids are gonna love it. - Sorry I'm late.
- 每月总有那么一天 - 话说昨晚上怎么样?
- Ugh, we hear that once a month. - So how did it go last night?
一般 我们喝了汤 他洒了一裤裆
Typical. We had soup, and he spooged in his pants.
喂?
Hello?
Lucy 我那贱姐
Lucy! It's my bitch sister.
好多年没联系了 你还好吗?
It's been years. How are you?
我一直... 一直想给你打电话来着
I've... I've been meaning to call you.
美国著名影星 教父系列电影主演之一
就跟家人搭阿尔·帕西诺的私人飞机去旅行啦
Just traveling with the family on Al Pacino's private jet.
我儿子Randy要参演他下一部电影了
Our son, Randy, is going to be in Al's next movie.
- 天呐 那真... - 当然 还有我老公Hubert
- Oh, wow. That's... - And then, of course, my husband, Hubert.
他刚把家里产业卖掉 现在我们有钱投资一座新岛屿了
He just sold his business, so now we're in the market for a new island.
本来要买海地 但那地方简直就是扶不起来的阿斗
We were going to buy Haiti, but it's too much of a fixer-upper.
说到那些黑人穷逼 你现在过得怎样?
Speaking of poor black people, how are you?
我也嫁了个好人家了
Oh, I'm married with a great family too!
你成家了? 是在避孕套上开了洞 还是被五个男人给轮了?
You have a family? Did you bite a hole in the condom or have a five-guy cream pie?
开玩笑啦 我都等不及见他们了
Just kidding. I can't wait to meet them.
我们这就改航 马上去你那儿看你啦
We're turning this plane around. We're coming to see you.
别介别介别介 不要 不... 不用这样
Oh, no, no. Don't! Uh, uh... don't... don't do that.
我的老天
Oh, my God!
- Lucy 听着 我... - 不 我Ken
- Lucy, listen. I... - Nah, it's Ken.
昨晚上真不好意思
Sorry about last night.
不如你现在过来让我补偿你吧?
Why don't you come over now and I'll make it up to you?
我会扑倒你 然后...
I'll bend you over and...
好了 没事了 不用过来了
Okay, done. No need to come over.
这就是身为林警的职责所在
And that's what it means to be a Park Ranger.
讲的太好了 Steve
That was great, Steve.
我要好好感谢你
I want to thank you.
还在犹豫什么 威武林警?
What are you waiting for, Power Ranger?
快上嘛 Steve 求插入
Go ahead, Steve. Stick it in me.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
我刚做了一场超赞美梦
I was having the best dream!
我特么玩完了
I am so screwed.
我老姐跟她老公正往脆莓这边赶呢
My sister and her husband are on their way to Brickleberry right now.
我不知道你还有个姐
I didn't know you had a sister.
那是因为我一直都想让她滚出我的生活
That's because I've been trying to wish her out of my life.
嘿 Ethel 只要100刀 我就让你美梦成真
Hey, Ethel. For 100 bucks, I can make that wish come true.
我已经好久没有满足过我的黑暗面了
It's been a while since I fed my dark passenger.
不管怎么说 我姐让我抓狂死了
So anyway, my sister makes me crazy.
尽我们一生 她什么事儿都比我待遇好
I mean, our whole lives, she's always had it better than me.
恭喜了 你们生下了一个完美 漂亮的女婴
Congratulations. You're the parents of a perfect, beautiful baby girl.
还有这玩意 要我把它扔了么?
And this thing. Uh, should I toss it?
看我们干啥? 圣诞老人偏爱她
What could we do? Santa loves her more.
你看起来真美 Lucy
You look beautiful, Lucy.
♪ 我喜欢蕊蕊 ♪
♪ I like vagina. ♪
她就在路上了 我要怎么办?
Oh, she's on your way. What am I gonna do?
有了 你们可以来个人假扮我老公啊
I know. One of you could pose as my husband.
- Woody? - 滚
- Woody? - No!
- Steve? - 抱歉 心有所属
- Steve? - Sorry. Already in love.
上哪儿能找着个老公啊?
Where am I gonna find a husband?
种族歧视贱人 拿哥当墨西哥佬一类的对待
Racist bitch. Treating me like I'm a Mexican or something.
上哪儿能找着个老公啊?
Where am I gonna find a husband?
还得找个孩子
And I need a kid.
嘿 你 小孩
Hey! Psst. Little boy.
谁想吃糖糖吗?
Do you want some candy?
- 抓到你了 - 救命 爸爸
- Gotcha! - Help, daddy!
离我孩子远点 你吃错药了吧?
Get away from my kid! What's the matter with you?
我非常需要你儿子
I want your son. Bad!
不差钱
I've got money!
不 等等 你也可以一起来假扮我老公
No! Wait! You can join in and play my husband!
求求你了
Please.
还有继续约会的念头 真难得啊
That's good to see you're dating again.
欢迎来到脆莓公园
Welcome to Brickleberry Park.
谢谢
Thank you.
事业单位为弱势群体提供部分岗位
这公园还雇智障真是良心啊
It's so nice they hire the mentally challenged.
假的啦 我讨厌智障
Not really. I hate them.
天呐 他们都来了
Oh, my God, they're here.
咋的?
What?
不要 不要
No! No!
你想干嘛?
No, what are you doing?
离我远点
Get away from me!
救命
Help!
Ethel 天呐 能见到你实在太好了
Ethel. Oh, my God. It's so nice to see you.
这就是我小侄儿了吧
This must be my nephew.
你死定了
You are dead.
小淘气包儿今天没睡午觉呀
Little cranky pants didn't have his nap.
我特么非得把你眼珠子挖出来
I am gonna [Bleep] claw your eyes out!
有天赋的小孩脾气都挺大
Tantrums are normal for gifted kids.
谁尼玛小孩 我可是野兽
I'm not a kid. I'm a wild animal.
想象力还超级丰富 还有多动症
And he has such colorful imagination. Well, and ADHD.
去玩吧 亲爱的
Go play, honey.
好吧
Uh, okay.
还有你一直和我们津津乐道的老公呢?
Now where's that husband you were telling me so much about?
对 他在...
Uh, yeah. He's...
我回来了 亲爱的
I'm right here, honey.
我是Conner
Hi, I'm Conner.
Ethel亲爱的老公
Ethel's loving husband.
那啥 我看Malloy现在安静多了
Well, I see Malloy's calmed down quite a bit.
我们家Malloy就这样 前一刻动若脱兔 下一刻就静若处子
That's our Malloy. Playful one minute, a perfectly well-behaved child the next.
我听见我血流声了
I can hear my blood.
他有低血糖
He's hypoglycemic.
那Conner 你是做什么工作的?
So, Conner, what do you do for a living?
- 脑部手术 - 针对超模的妇科医生
- Brain surgeon. - Gynecologist for supermodels.
到底哪个啊?
Well, which is it?
是给妇科医生做脑部手术 还是给超模兼脑科医生当妇科大夫?
You do brain surgery on gynecologists or gynecology on supermodel brain surgeons?
我是做机器人的
I build robots.
这周的球赛你看了没?
So how about those packers this week?
球赛? 最近的赛季要等五个月才开赛呢
Packers? Football season doesn't start for five months.
我知道 我是想说... 那个...
I know. I was talking about the, uh...
那些同性恋
Fudge-packers.
傻缺同性恋还想结婚 闹呢吧?
Stupid homos want to get married. Am I right?
Conner
Conner!
是不是该送Malloy上学去了? 就这会儿?
Isn't it time to get Malloy to school? Like, right now?
我们上的是天才学校 他是神童
It's a school for the gifted. He's a prodigy.
我蛮想看看他学校的 介意我们一道吗?
Oh, I'd love to see his school. Mind if I tag along?
不去特么没理由啊
I don't see why the hell not.
Hazelhurst小学
好了 到了 好好学习天天向上 宝贝
Okay, here we are. Have a good day, baby.
嘿 瞧瞧这是谁
Hey, look who it is.
是个新来的
It's the new kid.
嘿 新来的 "丑人镇"来电话
Hey, new kid. Ugly town called.
说你当选镇长啦
You just got voted Mayor.
这得多丑才能当镇长啊
Think about how ugly that means he is.
"拉稀镇"的镇长也是你哦
You're also Mayor of diarrhea town.
犀利啊
Aw, snap!
那种地方真是龊到底了
That's the worst town I ever heard of.
我男朋友真幽默
My boyfriend is so funny.
这叫"女朋友" 你一辈子都不可能有的东西
This is called a girlfriend. Something you'll never have.
老大说他要不是基佬 就是有结婚恐惧症
Either he called him gay or he's got a fear of commitment.
听好了 小哥儿 接下来事情这么发展
Listen, buddy. Here's what's gonna happen.
首先 我会抢掉你的朋友
First, I'm gonna take your friends.
然后我会抢掉你女人
Then I'm gonna take your girlfriend.
到你一无所有的时候 我就宰了你
And when you have nothing left, I'm going to kill you.
真没想到 我挺喜欢上学
You know what? Think I'm gonna like school.
作为一名林警 直-直-捣
As a Park Ranger, it's pin-port-tint...
知道如何"操火"是很重要的
Important to know how to [Bleep] out a fire.
灭火
Put out a fire.
我靠 跟Stephanie肯定没戏了
Damn it! I'm gonna blow it with Stephanie.
别这样 Steve 好好想想我说的
Aw, come on. Steve. Think about what I said.
我不太确定诶 Denzel 脑补观众全裸对我没啥帮助
I don't know, Denzel. Imagining the audience naked really doesn't work for me.
咱就想帮帮你嘛
Just trying to help.
好吧 咱们换成B计划
All right, time for plan "B".
我先帮你热热场 相信我 绝对屌炸天
I'm gonna pump the kids up for you. Trust me, it's all about showmanship.
谢啦 兄弟
Thanks, man.
Woody 你也是来帮我准备演讲的?
Woody? You're here to help me with my speech too?
啥演讲?
What speech?
如果不是昨晚我喝麻了
Either I drank way too much last night or...
就是我乃狼人
Or I'm a Werewolf!
底线就是 我陪Ethel陪场作戏
So bottom line, I'm gonna go along with Ethel's charade
直到我解决掉那个小混蛋为止
long enough to destroy this bully's life.
嘿 Malloy 我懂的
Hey, Malloy. I've been there.
以前我也老被欺负
I used to get bullied too.
我老子总会来学校 抢走老妈给我的午饭钱
My old man would show up at school, take the lunch money my mom gave me,
拿电源线抽得我屁滚尿流
beat the piss out of me with an extension cord.
很丢人吧? 肯定的
Was it humiliating? Sure.
但我也给了他好看
But I showed him.
我开始享受挨抽的感觉
I started to enjoy the beatings.
性奋地享受
Sexually.
够啦 我不敢坐你大腿上了
Okay. I'm gonna get off your lap now.
这样交交心最舒服了
Great talk, son. Hey,
说起来 你是不是换发型了?
by the way, did you get a haircut?
好啦 孩子们 安静啦
All right, kids. Settle down.
马上登场是一位特别英俊潇洒的公园林警...
We're about to bring out a remarkably handsome Park Ranger to...
闭嘴吧 Steve女 接下来就交给我啦
Zip it, Beav-Steve. I'll take it from here.
药 跟着节拍
Yo, drop that beat!
动起来 小杂碎们
Yeah, mother[Bleep]!
都给我在这破屋子里骚-起来
It's time to get krunk up in this bitch!
♪ 丰乳肥臀 丰乳肥臀 ♪
♪ Ass and titties. Ass and titties. ♪
♪ 大屁股扭啊 大屁股晃 ♪
♪ Shake that ass. Drop that ass. ♪
♪ 抽 插 抽 插 ♪
♪ Slide, dip. Slide, dip. ♪
♪ 落地得分 便便屎黄 ♪
♪ Touch the ground. Doo doo brown!♪
有请Steve
And here's Steve.
好的
Okay.
我是林... 林警Steve
Uh, I'm ran... ranger Steve.
我... 我会详细给大家介绍一下林警的职责
And I-I'm gonna tell you all about being a Park Ranger.
"Park公园"和"Pork猪肉"音近
你那怂样更像猪肉佬好吧
You look more like a pork ranger.
犀利 他说猪肉佬
Snap! He said pork ranger!
真是好文采啊 哟
That's a play on words, yo!
好 好吧
Uh, okay.
作-作为林警 用-用火安全非常重要
As a... as a ranger, f-f-fire safety is important.
森林火灾极其危险
Forest fires are extremely dangerous.
你丫逼脸就被火毁容了吧?
Is that what [Bleep] your face up?
新来的爆粗口哟
New kid dropped an HBO word.
脑补大家都裸着 脑补大家都裸着
Picture everyone naked. Picture everyone naked.
脑补孩子都裸着?
Picturing kids naked?
你在家还没脑补够嘛 你个肥猪恋童癖?
Don't you do enough of that at home, you pudgy pedophile?
我去 赞 赞 赞
Oh, no! No, no, no, no!
他说人家肥 还喜欢摸鸡鸡
He's saying pork ranger's a pee-pee toucher.
他就咱大王啊
He is the King!
新大王
New King!
朋友都是我的啦 第一步
Got your friends. That's one.
咱们出去玩儿吧 宝贝
Let's get out of here, baby.
- 不行 话剧要排练 - 话剧哈?
- Can't. Play rehearsal. - Play, huh?
启动第二阶段
Initiate phase two.
奏乐送我 Denzel
Play me out, Denzel.
♪ 丰乳肥臀 丰乳肥臀 ♪
♪ Ass and titties. Ass and titties. ♪
♪ 操翻婊子 操翻婊子 ♪
♪ Hump dem hos, hump dem hos. ♪
♪ 丰乳肥臀 丰乳肥臀 ♪
♪ Ass and titties. Ass and titties. ♪
Malloy 今天上学好玩吗?
Well, Malloy. How was school today?
还不赖 我参加话剧的试镜了
Not bad. I'm auditioning for a part in a play.
我不喜欢话剧
I don't like plays.
只是想插班上的一个妹子而已
I'm just trying to get in this girl's guts in my class.
说来 Conner
So, Conner...
Ethel肯定跟你讲过我们在亚马逊雨林办的绝赞婚礼吧
I'm sure Ethel told you about our amazing wedding in the Amazon Rain Forest.
太小儿科了 咱俩是在月亮上结的婚
That's nothing. We got married on the moon.
墨西哥的旅游城市
她说的是坎昆的月宫
Uh, Moon Palace. Cancun.
那地儿贵得很哟
It was very pricey.
我怎么记着你说在夏威夷结的来着?
I thought you said you got married in Hawaii.
我们办了两场的嘛
Uh, we had two ceremonies.
好的那场没要黑鬼参加
They didn't want blacks at the good wedding.
对 不对
Right. No!
妈咪发火了
Mommy's got a temper.
- 她会打我 - 跳棋对打赛嘛
- She beats me. - At checkers.
- Ethel? - 这位谁?
- Ethel? - Who is this?
- 妈咪的男朋友 - 什么?
- Mommy's boyfriend. - Pardon?
你结婚了? 真够劲
You're married? That's hot.
咱再电联吧
I'll call you later.
你最好解释清楚 Ethel
You better explain yourself, Ethel.
是这样的...
Oh, there's a good...
那个 刚才啊...
Oh, you see, what happened...
够了 这谎我编不下去了
You know what? I can't lie anymore.
你说得对 咱们别再隐瞒了
You're right. Let's not lie anymore.
今天不是随随便便的日子
This just isn't any ordinary night.
今晚是我们的结婚周年纪念
Tonight's our anniversary.
我想送我爱的女人一件礼物
And I'd like to give something to the woman I love.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
那个真像奶奶的项链 我还以为她带进坟墓了呢
Well, it's just like grandma's necklace. I thought that was one of a kind.
你怎么知道我一直就想要这种的?
How did you know I always wanted one like this?
我偷了你日记 不对 是倾听了你
I stole your diary. I mean, I listen!
我还找着你丢了的日记本了
Oh, and I found your missing diary.
人家真够贴心 Ethel
He's so thoughtful, Ethel.
你可嫁了个好男人呀
You've got a good man, there.
是啊 的确
Yeah, I do.
矮油 爸爸妈妈今晚要啪啪啪了
Aw. Mommy and daddy are gonna rub holes tonight.
真希望我们能留下 但是你知道
Well, I wish we could stay, but you know.
阿尔·帕西诺还等着咱呢
Al Pacino's in a holding pattern.
Lucy 好啦 我们走吧
Lucy, come on. Let's go.
可别打扰这对鸳鸯鸟甜蜜蜜了
We gotta let these two lovebirds rub holes.
好啊 终于回到正常生活了
Oh, well. Back to our normal lives.
我恨正常生活
I hate our normal lives.
等等 你们不能走
Wait! You can't leave.
那岂不错过Malloy明天的精彩大戏了
You'll miss Malloy's big part in the play tomorrow
他是替补演员临时上的
He had to fill in last minute.
听他说男主那边出了点状况
He said something happened to the lead actor.
救命 救命
Help! Help!
今晚就留下跟我们住吧
You can just spend the night with us.
真是好主意 Conner
Great idea, Conner.
那也好 真等不及看我小侄儿表演呢
Oh, yes. I'd love to see my nephew in a play.
- 我超喜欢戏剧 - 就这么定了
- I just adore the theater. - Well, let's do it.
太好了 太好了 太好了
Oh, boy! Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
那我就能跟Ethel睡一张床了
That means I get to sleep in the bed with Ethel.
跟我们往常一样
Like we always do.
因为咱们是老公老婆
Because we're married.
还会在对方身体的咸湿幽谷中互探究竟
And we've explored every wet, dark crevice of each other's bodies.
- 晚安 你们三口 睡个好觉 - 晚安
- Good night, you three. Sleep well. - Good night.
- 傲娇婊 - 抱歉把你逼这份儿上 Ethel
- Uppity bitch. - Sorry I pulled this on you, Ethel.
我只是不希望这一切结束
I just don't want this to end.
知道吗 Connie?
You know what, Connie?
没关系 你帮了我这么多
It's okay. You've helped me out so much.
其实呢 这样还... 挺好的
Actually, this is kind of... nice.
我知道 我从没这么开心过
I know. I don't think I've ever been this happy.
说来悲催 我也这么觉得
You know, in a sad way, me too.
唯有一件事能让一切变得更美妙了
There's only one thing that could make this better.
Connie
Connie!
老天 这什么玩意儿啊?
Jesus! What the hell is that?
但不是说我们是一家人嘛
But I thought we were a real family.
Connie 醒醒吧
Connie, wake up!
这不是真的
This is not real.
你是拉拉 咱家孩子就一刮了毛儿的熊
You're a lesbian, and our child is a shaved bear.
我们和一家半点不沾边
We are nothing like a family.
那个早泄Ken随便给我来一发比你一辈子来的都强
Pre-Jack Ken would have a better shot at me than you ever will.
没事儿吧 你们俩?
Is everything okay in here?
有事
No.
Ethel 我要离婚
Ethel, I want a divorce!
- 啥? - 而且我要把项链拿回来
- What? - And I'm taking that necklace back.
- 你要怎么地 退回去吗? - 没错 就是
- What are you gonna do? Return it? - Yes, I am.
我会再把你奶奶挖出来 把这破项链捆回她脖子上
I'm gonna dig up your grandmother again and put it back on her [Bleep] neck!
随你
Fine.
等下 什么?
Wait, what?
话剧
真不敢相信你非逼我们到这儿来 Woody
I can't believe that you made us come to this, Woody.
我不能在Stephanie面前晃悠了
I can't show my face around Stephanie.
闭嘴 落腚 这可是我家小熊仔的处女秀
Zip it and sit down. It's my Cubby Wubb's first play.
你一定会喜欢上的
And you're gonna love it!
Steve 你的演讲好棒呢
Steve, your speech was awesome.
孩子们特喜欢 他们从没笑得这么开怀
The kids loved it. They never laughed so hard.
真的吗? 可是我都尿裤子了
You serious? But I peed my pants.
就是那个才最赞呢
That was the best part.
我都不知道现在有多少孩子想当林警了
I can't tell you how many kids want to be Rangers now.
真的吗? 有多少?
Really? How many?
说了 不知道呀 我又一个儿都没问
No, I can't tell you. I didn't ask any of them.
- 下一步该咋办 Denzel? - 我知道咋办 兄弟
- What should I do, Denzel? - I know what you should do, buddy.
去把自己给上了
Go [Bleep] yourself.
小话儿真贴心儿 兄弟
Thanks for the kind words, bro.
Con... ner 没想到...
Con... ner. I'm surprised to...
省省吧 Ethel 我只是过来捧儿子场的
Save it, Ethel. I'm just here to support our son.
离婚没什么不好的嘛
There's no shame in divorce.
只要你们不介意跟同性恋一起下地狱就行
As long as you don't mind burning in hell with the queers.
我们没事啦 对吧 亲爱的?
Everything is fine. Right, honey?
他就是懒得抬嘴
His tongue is tired.
口活累着了
Tons of oral.
咋着? 不插预告片?
What? No previews?
伊人将何去 罗密欧?
Wherefore art thou, Romeo?
怎么让他出演了?
How did he get in the play?
Jeremy怎么了?
What happened to Jeremy?
至少水停了
Well, at least the water stopped.
不要
No!
Denzel 上音乐
Denzel, make it happen.
让咱来给你的玉米卷撒点辣酱
This should put a little hot sauce on your taco.
只许看不许摸哟
You can look, but you can't touch.
喜欢吗?
You like that?
打赌你喜欢这朵翘臀
I bet you like this sweet ass.
把了你妹子 第二步
Got your girl. That's two.
万神Malloy把了你妹子
Magic Malloy stole your lady!
放开她
Get off her!
这剧屌炸天了
This play's awesome.
大家请冷静
Everyone, please calm down.
Malloy 够了
Malloy, break it up!
现在来办第三件
Here comes three.
救命
Help!
再来个 再来个
Encore! Encore!
非礼勿视 滚出滚出
Turn it off! Turn it off!
急救车
抱歉我咪咪蹦出来了 Ethel
Sorry my boobs popped out, Ethel.
Ethel 不敢相信你会骗我
Ethel, I can't believe you lied to me.
这是我在家人里见过最可悲的托辞
This is the sorriest excuse for a family I've ever seen.
你要是能有这么个家 算你走大运
You'd be lucky to have a family as great as this.
- 这话真心的 Ethel? - 非常不可能 Connie
- Do you really mean that, Ethel? - Probably not, Connie.
真温馨
That is sweet...
要多悲催有多悲催
how pathetic you are.
再也不见
Talk to you never.
你就打算这么放她走?
You're gonna let her get away with that?
没办法 Malloy
You know, Malloy,
有时候 做老大就是会吃香
sometimes it's better just to be the bigger person.
Malloy
Malloy!
欢迎微博关注@漫迪字幕组
weibo.com/weheartcartoons